Let me just clear this away , I 'll be back .
This place 's crazy , for real !
- It 's filled with hookers , man ! - That 's just typical of you , Eko .
What 's typical of me , Jimmy ?
You 've been on my ass since the start of this trip .
I got it ! You 're the guy with the car , shit !
Oh , Astrid , take my seat over here .
Eko , don 't be like that , please .
Saved by the bell , dude .
Where 's the mike ? Let 's crash this place !
How 's Ladya ?
More complicated than I thought .
Then let me talk to her ;
she 's practically a sister to me .
Okay ... I 'll go talk to her now .
Ladya ...
This is what mom and dad left us .
I 'll send for more .
What 's this for , Adjie ? I don 't need money .
You don 't need to live like this .
I 'll take care of everything .
You could live at mom and dad 's house .
And if you want to , get back to college .
You 're here to rescue me now ?
I 'm happy with the way things are .
They 've accepted me over in Australia .
We 'll be flying out tomorrow .
I wanted to say goodbye .
You came all the way over here just to tell me that ?
Astrid called me about this ,
- so there was no need for you to . - Ladya , please !
Can 't we just talk ? Like the old days ?
Listen , Adjie ...
Every time I see you ...
I think back to mom and dad , their accident ...
What could I do ?
They wouldn 't have caught that taxi , had it not been for you !
- Take good care of Astrid now ... - Ladya !
Hey , where 's our dessert ?
I 'm sorry , we don 't serve what you 've requested .
Then why don 't you be our dessert , sweetie ?
Careful : your boyfriend might get jealous .
She just called you a homo !
Wait a minute .
What 's with you ? Never tasted a man 's touch ?
- Bitch ! - You alright ? - I 'm okay .
You and me , outside .
Just so you know ... you 'll be a dead man .
Shithead !
That 's so typical of you , Alam .
If it wasn 't for me , you 'd be dead now !
Now what 's your excuse ? ! I should fire you !
- Sir , allow me . - Who 's this now ?
Customer 's safety should ...
have been your responsibility , right ?
I 'm gonna find that guy ! Cut him into pieces ! Bitch !
What 's the matter with you ?
- Are you alright ? - Yeah , nothing new there .
So , what time 's the flight ?
Tomorrow ... afternoon .
Are you okay to fly ?
It 's fine ... Should be nice to give birth there .
Boy or girl ?
I 've a feeling it 's a boy ...
though your brother prefers it to be a surprise .
We shall see ...
Oh yeah ...
For when the baby 's old enough .
Thank you , Aunt Ladya .
It 'd be nice if you gave it yourself , though ?
I 'm going to miss you so bad .
Take good care in Sydney .
Won 't you join us till the airport , then ?
We don 't know when we 'll meet again , right ?
It 'll be raining soon , honey .
Ah ! Someone 's decided to come after all .
Alam , you 're a happy camper now , eh ?
What the ... ? Just in time .
A storm out of nowhere .
To Jakarta ... with Ladya .
Alam 's happy .
- Off we go ! Oh , shit ! - Who 's she ?
She 's shivering ...
- Lemme out ! - Where are you going ?
To help her , damn it .
Eko , wait !
He 's always like this ... Guys , let 's stay out of this .
She says she 's been robbed .
- Where does she live ? - Dunno ; she 's all spaced out .
Uh , where do you live , miss ?
Where are you heading to ?
Would you like us to call a taxi , miss ?
We 're going to Jakarta .
Then ... you will pass my house .
Let 's help her .
I 'm not sure , honey .
She 's just a girl , all alone . We can 't leave her , right ?
Okay , okay .
Miss , let us take you home , then .
Just point out the way , okay ? Take a seat .
What now ?
Lemme drive , man .
Be a bro , dammit .
- Sorry , Astrid ... - It 's okay .
Freaking baldie !
Miss , what 's your name ?
Maya .
- What 's wrong ? - Nothing .
Maya , are we going the right way ?
We 've arrived .
Would you like to come in ?
Thanks , but we 're fine .
I want to introduce you to Mother .
Just to greet her .
It won 't take long .
Would you ... Eko ?
Uh ... sure .
Let me call Mother .
The house smells like stale farts !
You seem so tense ... What 's up ?
Nothing . It feels rather weird , though .
Ease up .
We 'll be on our way soon . Okay ?
Everyone , this is Mother .
- I am Dara . - Adjie .
Astrid .
How old is the baby ?
About 8 months now .
My deepest gratitude for bringing Maya back home .
We couldn 't just leave her there by herself .
Please stay for a bit .
The baby could use some rest .
I want to prepare a simple meal , as token of our gratitude .
No need for that , ma 'am . We ought to get ready anyway .
I must insist : I won 't allow myself to be rude ,
so allow me to repay your kindness .
Take a short rest ...
before resuming your journey .
It 's alright , Adjie .
You must all be hungry .
You still have quite a distance to go .
Maybe we could use a little rest .
Sorry , but can I use the bathroom ?
Maya , would you take him upstairs ?
Please excuse me .
You could 've just said " No , thank you " .
We 'd be on our way now .
Sorry , man .
It 's fine , dear . Seems like it 's going to rain , anyhow .
Yeah , bro ... I could use some grub .
Right .
Lam , can I get a light ?
- Just hold on to it . - Cheers .
You scared me , jerk ! Get a life .
Should 've seen your face . Classic moment !
This place must be very old : look at those photos .
Jim !
Cool , huh ?
It looks kinda sharp , Lam !
Serious killer , this one .
Careful !
Look : original Japanese . Razor sharp , eh ?
Yeah , just put it back , man .
Too damn cool ...
Excuse me .
It 's an old keepsake , very fragile .
He didn 't mean anything by it .
Did I scare you out there ?
No , I was just ... I didn 't want to intrude .
Thank you for helping my sister .
- Maya , she 's your sister ? - Yes . I 'm Adam .
Ladya .
And your friends ?
That 's Jimmy and Alam . Sorry , they 're harmless .
It 's alright . No harm done .
It 's rare for someone to help others nowadays ,
even in the case of accidents .
The tattoo : is there a meaning ?
This ? Not at all , I just like the design .
Do you like tattoos ?
I like to look at them ... but I 'm afraid of having one .
May I touch it ?
Sure .
Please drink this .
Dinner 's ready .
You may come with us now .
Actually , if it 's alright I 'd rather just rest here .
Alright , dear ?
We have a guest room upstairs .
Maya , take her upstairs .
Follow me , please .
I 'll be fine , dear , just go and eat .
Honey , wait ! Actually , I 'll stay with my wife .
My friends will stay for dinner . Thank you .
Where are you going ?
I 'll catch up , honey .
I 'm staying with Astrid .
After you 're done , let 's just roll , okay ?
Please .
I 'll leave you for now .
Thank you , Maya .
This is Arman .
To our guests !
Thank you for helping one of us .
Please accept our small token of gratitude .
You may begin .
You made this all yourself ?
Damn , this is some gourmet meat ! Definitely 5-star quality .
Alam , you must try that one .
Nice necklace ; does it signify something ?
This family heirloom has been passed on for many generations .
Why can 't she get past it ? Think of her future instead .
Easy on yourself , dear .
Eventually , everything will work out .
You 're okay ?
The baby 's kicking hard .
It 's a girl , for sure .
- How would you know ? - A talker , just like her mom .
This wine must be really vintage . My head 's spinning .
But damn , it 's good !
Eko , why don 't you just spend the night here ?
Uh , sure ... yeah .
Mother , may I be excused ?
Ladya , try this .
Let me try it .
Tastes rather unique .
I don 't think I can finish this . I 'm quite full .
The other guests ...
They never finished either .
How old are you , anyway ?
How old would you think I am ?
What 's wrong , Eko ?
Arman , take them downstairs .
Adam , prepare the tools .
We have the first pick-up soon .
You 're awake .
Where are the others ?
Your friends ?
They 're upstairs .
Yeah ?
I 'm going up , then .
Alam .
Just wait .
We never really got to talk .
Why is that ?
Ladya 's upstairs , too ?
What is it with her ?
Just come with me .
Wouldn 't you like ... to have a taste ...
of what you 're looking at now ?
L-I just wanted to know where the others are ...
I told you : they 're upstairs .
Why would you want to leave me all alone ?
I just want to see my friends !
Eko , where the hell are you ?
What now ?
What 's so wrong with me ?
- Wait ... - Why ? !
What , huh ? What 's wrong with me ? !
Jimmy !
Alam ... ?
Alam !
What do you want ? ! Huh ?
What about now ?
I 'll stab you ! I swear I will ! Stay away .
Alam ?
Alam !
Adjie !
Go to the room !
Adjie ? !
- Ladya , wake up ! - Shh , Ladya !
It stinks in here ...
Where are we ?
Alam ! Adjie !
Where the hell is everyone ? !
- That bitch ... this is all her doing ! - This is your fault !
Hey ! What do you want from us ? !
We 'll pay ! We have money !
Call , just call them !
Ladya ! Be careful !
Jimmy ...
Alam ... it 's Alam !
Alam , we 're in here !
We 're all tied up , help us !
Eko ?
Ladya , what 's going on , dammit ? !
- The guy with glasses ... - Call him , Ladya ! - No ! - Why ?
No ... no !
Alam ?
Please , God , no ...
He 's dead .
Why are you doing this ? !
I 'm here , dear !
Adjie !
Astrid ...
The father of your child is alright .
Stay there , dear ! Don 't come out !
Adjie ! ?
Don 't hurt Astrid .
Adjie !
Adjie ! Don 't touch him !
Your kindness towards Maya ...
brought all of you here tonight .
Thank you , Astrid .
No ... not Ladya !
Let Ladya go !
I don 't want to die ... please .
You fat son of a bitch ! Eko , come on !
You damn pig ! Fat bastard !
Come on , you fat shit ! Let Ladya go !
Let her go ...
Help !
Please help us here !
Good ... everything is complete .
Lady Dara ?
She 's preoccupied right now .
She sends her kindest regards to them .
Help !
Do you feel it , Astrid ?
As of now , you can only rely on yourself .
What you drank earlier ...
will aid you in getting through this .
Have no fear ...
A woman 's strength is such that few can imagine .
Your pain right now ...
pales to insignificance compared to what you 'll deliver to this earth .
All your questions will soon be answered .
Are you hearing that ?
My baby !
Astrid !
Where are we ?
Wait ! We can 't !
Where the hell ?
The house !
Come on !
Eko !
- Where 's your car , Jim ? - Huh ? My car ... ?
Jim ?
Ladya ? Where the hell , man ? !
Maya ?
Ah ! Ah ! My ear !
- Shit ! Bitch ! - We got to run , Eko !
Eko , wait !
Eko ! Ladya , faster !
Ladya ... ? Where 's Ladya , Eko ? !
Ladya !
Jim !
How are we going to get outta here , Jim ?
'Adv a " .
I can 't take this shit anymore !
Eko " .Eko !
Everyone 's dead , Jim ! They 're all dead !
Ladya 's all alone out there !
- Dead ... all dead ! - Stop saying that !
We ... we have to ...
Jim ... Where you going , man ?
Ladya , she 's out there ...
Don 't leave me , man !
Jim !
You stay put !
Slowly , Jim ...
Watch your step .
Quick ... Everything 's going to be ...
Jimmy ...
Ladya .
Run , Ladya !
Jimmy !
Huh ? Jimmy ?
Adjie !
Wake up ...
Stop !
Not my baby ...
I can imagine the pain you are going through .
A mother ...
who has to lose her child ...
Not even a name given ...
I 'm giving you one chance .
Take a look at your husband .
Help him ...
and maybe you two can get out of here ...
and live longer .
Should you choose the child ,
I promise you ,
all of you will be finished tonight .
Please ...
The child is no longer yours .
Astrid ?
Dear ... ?
Astrid !
Adjie !
Hold it honey ! Don 't let go !
Our baby ... It 's a boy ...
Sleep , my child .
It shouldn 't have ended like this .
You bitch ! Die !
Mother ...
May I help you ?
Sorry , sir .
My name is Syarief . This here 's my unit .
Are you the owner of this villa ?
We have been living here for a while , sir .
Would you come over here , ma 'am ?
Who 's that bald man ?
He 's one of the students who are renting rooms here , sir .
He 's from Jakarta .
A Jakarta kid , huh ?
No wonder ...
We found him by the road .
I 'd like to know how he ended up there .
I asked for his help , sir .
My dog went missing in the forest .
Dog , you said ? Anyone see a dog ?
- No , sir ! - Didn 't see any , sir .
- I asked him to look for it . - Sure you did .
Um , could you tell me how many rooms there are ?
You won 't mind if I take a quick look around , right ?
You see , they 're all top cops .
Including me .
I almost forgot ...
Allow me to introduce myself . My name is Sonny ...
Sonny Samba .
Why don 't we bring the boy back in ?
The poor boy must be freezing .
Sure thing , ma 'am .
Alright , ma 'am .
As you know , it 's our duty to fully investigate matters like this .
Though could I request that the other kids don 't cause any more trouble ?
So , are we clear of any problems then , sir ?
No problem at all , ma 'am .
- Petrus ! - Yes , sir !
Always with that damn phone ! Bring the bald one in !
Right away , sir !
Wake up . Let 's see the this necklace .
- Yes , sir ! - What the hell are you doing ?
- Help me out ! - I 'm waking baldie up , sir !
- Don 't you try anything funny . - I won 't sir , I promise . - Quick , now !
Baldie , wake up , wake up now ! Quickly !
- Baldie ! Wake up ! - Quick , I said !
Jeez ! Okay , I 'm getting down now , just chill ...
He 's just unconscious . He 'll be back up in no time .
He 's fortunate that I 'm not dragging him down to the station .
You 're very understanding , sir .
What 's that sound ?
- Taufiq , check it out . - Yes , sir .
Sir ... are you alright ?
Sir ?
Sir ...
Sir ... What 's wrong ?
Dear God ... Are you okay ?
Something 's fishy in this house ...
Sir ?
Taufiq ! Sonny !
Mr Policeman ...
Oh , Miss . What 's with the blackout , miss ?
Sonny !
Taufiq !
Shit . Where the hell ... Sonny !
Taufiq ! Freeze !
Shit . Shit . Shitl !
- What a mess , what an awful mess ... - We 're so screwed ...
Shit ! This isn 't right ! Let 's go , man !
- Shut the hell up and stay close ! - I 'll shut up , okay !
- Let 's go ! - Right bro , let 's go ...
Lets roll . I 'm here ... I 'm here ...
Taufiq ! Taufiq !
Sonny , where the hell are you ? !
Sonny , what 's wrong ? !
Bro , get up ! Stand up - he 's coming !
Freeze !
Shit !
Petrus ... Damn !
Come on , Sonny ! Quick ! Those bastards !
Syarief ?
Ma .
Help me , ma 'am ...
Help me , sir ..
Where is it ? !
Hey , slut !
Die , bitch !
Bitch !
M-mommy ... mommy ...
My child ...
Adjie ?
Adjie ...
My son ...
Astrid , oh God ...
They 're upstairs .
Adam ...
Bring me their heads .
Get the hell away from her !
Die ! You bitch !
Adam !
Adjie , watch out !
Adjie !
Adjie , I 'm so sorry , man . Forgive me .
'Adv a " .
Everything ends right here , Ladya .
Adjie ! I wanna go home !
Please ... home !
Eko !
Ladya !
Look at all this .
Look at what you 've caused tonight ...
- Where 's the baby ? - No !
You 'll never touch him !
Why are you doing this ?
Why can 't you just let us go ? !
They want you ... because they want to live longer .
You ...
You 've tasted it ...
TASTY , RIGHT ? !
Adjie !
Ladya ... watch ...
Watch over my son ...
Don 't leave me , Adjie .
Don 't leave me , don 't go ...
Forgive me ...
Unit 04 ... please report to base .
Unit 04 ... Where are you guys patrolling ? Please respond .
H ... hello ?
Hello ...
Let 's go home ...